adesignaward.com 2019-06-14

# A' Design Award and Competition - Privacy Policy

****Your privacy is critically important to us. At A' Design Award and Competition we have a few fundamental principles:

  * We don’t ask you for personal information unless we truly need it. 
  * We don’t share your personal information with anyone except to comply with the law, develop our products, or protect our rights.
  * We don’t store personal information on our servers unless required for the on-going operation of one of our services.
  * In our profile pages and portfolio creation products, we aim to make it as simple as possible for you to control what’s visible to the public, seen by search engines, kept private, and permanently deleted.

Below is our privacy policy which incorporates these goals:

OMC Design Studios SRL owner of A' Design Award and Competitions (“ **A' Design Award and Competition** ”) operates several websites including [adesignaward.com](https://competition.adesignaward.com/), [adesigncompetition.com](http://www.adesigncompetition.com/), [ adesignawards.com](http://www.adesignawards.com/), and [adesigncompetitions.com](http://www.adesigncompetitions.com/). It is A' Design Award and Competition’s policy to respect your privacy regarding any information we may collect while operating our websites.

Website Visitors

Like most website operators, A' Design Award and Competition collects non-personally-identifying information of the sort that web browsers and servers typically make available, such as the browser type, language preference, referring site, and the date and time of each visitor request. A' Design Award and Competition’s purpose in collecting non-personally identifying information is to better understand how A' Design Award and Competition’s visitors use its website. From time to time, A' Design Award and Competition may release non-personally-identifying information in the aggregate, e.g., by publishing a report on trends in the usage of its website.

A' Design Award and Competition also collects potentially personally-identifying information like Internet Protocol (IP) addresses. A' Design Award and Competition does not use such information to identify its visitors, however, and does not disclose such information, other than under the same circumstances that it uses and discloses personally-identifying information, as described below.

Gathering of Personally-Identifying Information

Certain visitors to A' Design Award and Competition’s websites choose to interact with A' Design Award and Competition in ways that require A' Design Award and Competition to gather personally-identifying information. The amount and type of information that A' Design Award and Competition gathers depends on the nature of the interaction. For example, we ask visitors who register at [adesignaward.com](https://competition.adesignaward.com/) to provide a username and email address. Those who engage in transactions with A' Design Award and Competition – by purchasing design competition joining and controlling service, for example – are asked to provide additional information, including as necessary the personal and financial information required to process those transactions. In each case, A' Design Award and Competition collects such information only insofar as is necessary or appropriate to fulfill the purpose of the visitor’s interaction with A' Design Award and Competition. A' Design Award and Competition does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below. And visitors can always refuse to supply personally-identifying information, with the caveat that it may prevent them from engaging in certain website-related activities.

Aggregated Statistics

A' Design Award and Competition may collect statistics about the behavior of visitors to its websites. For instance, A' Design Award and Competition may monitor the most popular designers on the ADesignAward.com site. A' Design Award and Competition may display this information publicly or provide it to others. However, A' Design Award and Competition does not disclose personally-identifying information other than as described below.

Protection of Certain Personally-Identifying Information

A' Design Award and Competition discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only to those of its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations that (i) need to know that information in order to process it on A' Design Award and Competition’s behalf or to provide services available at A' Design Award and Competition’s websites, and (ii) that have agreed not to disclose it to others. Some of those employees, contractors and affiliated organizations may be located outside of your home country; by using A' Design Award and Competition’s websites, you consent to the transfer of such information to them. A' Design Award and Competition will not rent or sell potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information to anyone. Other than to its employees, contractors and affiliated organizations, as described above, A' Design Award and Competition discloses potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information only when required to do so by law, or when A' Design Award and Competition believes in good faith that disclosure is reasonably necessary to protect the property or rights of A' Design Award and Competition, third parties or the public at large. If you are a registered user of an A' Design Award and Competition website and have supplied your email address, A' Design Award and Competition may occasionally send you an email to tell you about new features, solicit your feedback, or just keep you up to date with what’s going on with A' Design Award and Competition and our products. We primarily use our various product blogs to communicate this type of information, so we expect to keep this type of email to a minimum. If you send us a request (for example via a support email or via one of our feedback mechanisms), we reserve the right to publish it in order to help us clarify or respond to your request or to help us support other users. A' Design Award and Competition takes all measures reasonably necessary to protect against the unauthorized access, use, alteration or destruction of potentially personally-identifying and personally-identifying information.

**When you Make a Payment**

If you make a payment, we will save in our database all the information regarding the transaction to the extend permitted by law, that would include card holder or payer name, surname, partial (such as last 4 digits) card numbers, payment methods, payment accounts and other identifiable information. 

Cookies

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. A' Design Award and Competition uses cookies to help A' Design Award and Competition identify and track visitors, their usage of A' Design Award and Competition website, and their website access preferences. A' Design Award and Competition visitors who do not wish to have cookies placed on their computers should set their browsers to refuse cookies before using A' Design Award and Competition’s websites, with the drawback that certain features of A' Design Award and Competition’s websites may not function properly without the aid of cookies.

Ads

Ads appearing on any of our websites may be delivered to users by advertising partners, who may set cookies. These cookies allow the ad server to recognize your computer each time they send you an online advertisement to compile information about you or others who use your computer. This information allows ad networks to, among other things, deliver targeted advertisements that they believe will be of most interest to you. This Privacy Policy covers the use of cookies by A' Design Award and Competition and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers.

Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, A' Design Award and Competition may change its Privacy Policy from time to time, and in A' Design Award and Competition’s sole discretion. A' Design Award and Competition encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes to its Privacy Policy. If you have a [adesignaward.com](https://competition.adesignaward.com/) account, you should also check your designer "hidden cabinet" (dashboard) for alerts to these changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.
